bia2music.com 2014-12-29

# Privacy Policy | Bia2.com

Bia2! respects your right to the privacy of the personal information you provide us on our Web sites. To that end, unless you designate otherwise or we state otherwise in this policy or at the time information is collected, any personal information you provide to Bia2! will be known only to two parties: you and Bia2!. The following policy is intended to explain how your personal information will be treated as you make use of our sites and their features. Personal information includes your name, street and e-mail addresses, billing information, click-through activity and any other personal information you may provide here. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.

### Traffic data

Each time a visitor comes to Bia2!, our servers -- like most on the Web -- collect some basic technical information, including, for example, the visitor's domain name (e.g., whether the user is logged on from google.com or yahoo.com), referral data (e.g., we record the address of the last URL a user visited prior to clicking through to Bia2! Web site) and browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform).

We also count, track and aggregate the visitor's activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our sites (e.g. tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the Bia2.com, etc.). To these ends, we may merge information about visitors and visits into group data, which may then be shared on an aggregated basis with our advertisers; but we will not disclose your individual identity or personally identifiable data without your permission. When we do present aggregated information to outside companies, no one will be able to identify you or contact you. 

### Other disclosure of personal information

Bia2! will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information without your consent except (i) as described in this privacy policy, or (ii) as required by law, court order or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority. This policy does not protect information you post to any on-line bulletin board, chat room, newsgroup or other public forum within our Web sites.

### Cookies

Bia2! may set and access Bia2! cookies on your computer.   
Bia2! lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Bia2!'s cookies. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

### Other sites

Bia2! contains many links to other sites on the Web. We cannot control and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other Web sites.
